Finding aid to the Classes of 1951-1960 records CA.MS.01024
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1951-1960 records
1947-2010
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1951.
CA.MS.01024
39.5 linear feet (84 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Box 2195.2 is restricted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1951-1960 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College -- Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College -- Students.; Smith College. Class of 1952.; Smith College. Class of 1953.; Smith College. Class of 1954.; Smith College. Class of 1955.; Smith College. Class of 1956.; Smith College. Class of 1957.; Smith College. Class of 1958.; Smith College. Class of 1959.; Smith College. Class of 1960.; Smith College -- Students.; Smith College -- Alumni and alumnae.
- Class of 1951 Records, 1947-2002; 2.667 linear feet (7 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1951 was the seventy-third graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1951 Records, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1951, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - Commencement, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Music, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 4)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1947-1948 (Box 2175, Folder 6)
  - Groups, 1947-1951 (Box 2175, Folder 7)
  - History, 1947 (Box 2175, Folder 8)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 11)
  - Class Letters, 1967-1976; 2002 (Box 2175, Folder 12)
  - Officers, 1951 (Box 2175, Folder 13)
  - Organization (Box 2175, Folder 14)
    General
    See Class of 1949 Organization
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 2175, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 2175, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 2175, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 2175, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 2175, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1976 (Box 2175, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1976-1981 (Box 2175, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1981 (Box 2175, Folder 22)
  - 50th Reunion Book, 2001 (Box 2175.1, Folder 1)
  - 50th Reunion Book Addendum/Errata, 2001 (Box 2175.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Correspondence Newsletters (Box 2175, Folder 23)
  - Songs, 1996-2001 (Box 2175, Folder 24)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1949-1951; undated (Box 2175, Folder 25)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1949 (Box 2175, Folder 26)
  - Step Sings, 1949 (Box 2175, Folder 27)
  - Who's Who, 1947 (Box 2175, Folder 28)
  - Individuals A-P (Box 2176)
  - Individuals Q-Z (Box 2179)
  - Harrison, Anne (class notes) (Box 2177)
  - Hidden, Mary (Box 2178)
  - Tracy (Addis), Susan Silliman (music scores, speeches, correspondence) (Box 2178.1)
- Class of 1952 Records, 1948-2002; 3.875 linear feet (9 containers)
  The Class of 1952 was the seventy-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1952 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1952, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Music, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1948-1949 (Box 2180, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1948 (Box 2180, Folder 6)
  - Groups, 1948-1952 (Box 2180, Folder 7)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 8)
  - Ivy Day, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1951 (Box 2180, Folder 11)
  - Junior Ushers, 1951 (Box 2180, Folder 12)
  - Last Sing, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters, 1963-2002 (Box 2180, Folder 14)
  - Officers, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 15)
  - Organization (Box 2180, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 2180, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 2180, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 2180, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1977 (Box 2180, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1977-1982 (Box 2180, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 2180, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2180, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1997-2002 (Box 2180, Folder 24)
  - 50th Reunion, 2002 (Box 2180.1)
  - Reunions-"Penelope's Odyssey", 2002 (Box 2180, Folder 25)
  - Reunions-JYA Paris Reunion, 2002 (Box 2180, Folder 26)
  - Scrapbook (Box 2187.3)
  - Senior Dramatics-Marco's Millions, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 27)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2180, Folder 28)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1950 (Box 2180, Folder 29)
  - Class Supper, 1952 (Box 2180, Folder 30)
  - Who's Who, 1948 (Box 2180, Folder 31)
  - Individuals A-J (Box 2181)
  - Individuals K-Z (Box 2182)
  - Allison, Mary (letters home to family, letters from JYA France) (Box 2187.4)
  - Chauncey, Lucy Lawrence (book "A Selection of Letters Received After Her Death") (Box 1683.1)
  - Unknown (A Selection of Letters Received after her Death) (Box 2187.1)
  - Unknown (The Chauncey Family Archives 1669-1993, by Tammy Gobert and Henry Chauncey) (Box 2187.2)
- Class of 1953 Records, 1949-2003; 8 boxes (5 linear feet)
  The Class of 1953 was the seventy-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1953 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1953, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, extensive correspondences, and other memorabilia.
  - Alumnae Association-General, 1978 (Box 2188, Folder 1)
  - Alumnae Funds, 1967-1968 (Box 2188, Folder 2)
  - Alumnae Funds, 1969-1976 (Box 2188, Folder 3)
  - Alumnae Funds, 1977-1978 (Box 2188, Folder 4)
  - Alumnae Funds, 1981-1993 (Box 2188, Folder 5)
  - Alumnae Leadership on Council, 1988-1989 (Box 2188, Folder 6)
  - Alumnae Leadership on Council, 1989-1990 (Box 2188, Folder 7)
  - Alumnae Leadership on Council, 1990-1991 (Box 2188, Folder 8)
  - Alumnae Leadership on Council, 1992-1993 (Box 2188, Folder 9)
  - Class Baby, 1992 (Box 2188, Folder 10)
  - Class Bequest Program, 1975-1991 (Box 2188, Folder 11)
  - Class Book and scrapbooks (Box 2192.6)
  - Class Book and scrapbooks (Box 2192.7)
  - Class Book and scrapbooks (Box 2192.8)
  - Bylaws, undated (Box 2188, Folder 12)
  - Commencement, 1953 (Box 2188, Folder 13)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, 1953 (Box 2188, Folder 14)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1953 (Box 2188, Folder 15)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1953 (Box 2188, Folder 16)
  - Convocation, 1949 (Box 2188, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Association, 1953-1959 (Box 2188, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Association, 1960-1969 (Box 2188, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Association, 1970-1979 (Box 2188, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Association, 1987-1988 (Box 2188, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Association, 1992-1993 (Box 2188, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1953-1960 (Box 2188, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1961-1962 (Box 2188, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1963-1967 (Box 2188, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1968-1969 (Box 2188, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1970-1976 (Box 2188, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1977-1979 (Box 2188, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1980-1981 (Box 2188, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1982-1983 (Box 2188, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1984-1985 (Box 2188, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1987-1988 (Box 2188, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1988-1989 (Box 2188, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1990-1991 (Box 2188, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-Alumnae Funds, 1992-1993 (Box 2188, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1953-1963 (Box 2189, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1966-1967 (Box 2189, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1968-1969 (Box 2189, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1970-1971 (Box 2189, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1972-1976 (Box 2189, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1977-1978 (Box 2189, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1979-1980 (Box 2189, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1981-1982 (Box 2189, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1983-1984 (Box 2189, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1987-1988 (Box 2189, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1988-1989 (Box 2189, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1989-1990 (Box 2189, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1990-1991 (Box 2189, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1991-1992 (Box 2189, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence-Class Officers, 1993-1994 (Box 2189, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence-Racial Issues at Smith, 1988 (Box 2189, Folder 16)
  - Daughters of Smith Alums Enrolled at Smith, undated (Box 2189, Folder 17)
  - Employment Status, 1953 (Box 2189, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1949-1950 (Box 2189, Folder 19)
  - General, 1952 (Box 2189, Folder 20)
  - Groups, 1949-1953; 1991-1992 (Box 2189, Folder 21)
  - History, 1949-1953 (Box 2189, Folder 22)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1953 (Box 2189, Folder 23)
  - House Representatives, 1977-1982 (Box 2189, Folder 24)
  - Ivy Day, 1953 (Box 2189, Folder 25)
  - Junior Ushers, 1952 (Box 2189, Folder 26)
  - Class Letters, 1953-1959 (Box 2189, Folder 27)
  - Class Letters, 1960-1969 (Box 2189, Folder 28)
  - Class Letters, 1970-1979 (Box 2189, Folder 29)
  - Class Letters, 1980-1989 (Box 2189, Folder 30)
  - Class Letters, 1990-2003 (Box 2189, Folder 31)
  - Class Officers, 1950 (Box 2189, Folder 32)
  - Class Officers-Minutes, undated (Box 2189, Folder 33)
  - Organization (Box 2189, Folder 34)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 2189, Folder 35)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 2191, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1954 (Box 2191, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 2191, Folder 3)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1958 (Box 2191, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 2191, Folder 5)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1963 (Box 2191, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 2191, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 2191, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2191, Folder 9)
  - Reunions-Commencement Parade Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2191, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1973 (Box 2191, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1973 (Box 2191, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 2191, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 2191, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 2191, Folder 15)
  - Reunions-Geneva Group, 1978 (Box 2191, Folder 16)
  - 25th Reunion (photo album) (Box 2192.5)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2192, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1983 (Box 2192, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1983 (Box 2192, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1988 (Box 2192, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 2192, Folder 5)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 2192, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1993 (Box 2192, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1998 (Box 2192, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box 2192, Folder 9)
  - Reunions-50th, 2003 (Box 2192.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Book, 2003 (Box 2192.1, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships and Student Aid, 1966-1967 (Box 2189, Folder 36)
  - Smith Club Associations, 1967 (Box 2189, Folder 37)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2189, Folder 38)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1951 (Box 2189, Folder 39)
  - Step Sings, 1953 (Box 2189, Folder 40)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1968-1992 (Box 2189, Folder 41)
  - Who's Who, 1949 (Box 2189, Folder 42)
  - Individuals A-O (Box 2190)
  - Individuals P-Z (Box 2190.1)
  - Jones, Elizabeth (Scrapbooks), 1949-1951 (Box 2192.3)
  - Jones, Elizabeth (Scrapbooks), 1951-1953 (Box 2192.4)
  - Schulz, Helene Pringle ("Helene's Story") (Box 2192.2)
- Class of 1954 Records, 1950-2002; 3.125 linear feet (10 containers)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 2195.2 is restricted
  The Class of 1954 was the seventy-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1954 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1954, including materials from commencement, reunions, dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, extensive correspondences, questionnaires, financial information, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, "Covenant", 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, "Covenant", 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, "Covenant", 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 4)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, Photographs, 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 5)
  - Commencement-Music, 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 6)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 7)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1954 (Box 2193, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1980; undated (Box 2193, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 2193, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 2193, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box 2193, Folder 12)
  - Deferred Gifts and Bequests, 1975-1984 (Box 2193, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1950-1951 (Box 2193, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Reception, 1950 (Box 2193, Folder 15)
  - Class Fund Agent, 1965-1984 (Box 2193, Folder 16)
  - Groups, 1950-1954; 1978 (Box 2194, Folder 1)
  - History, 1950 (Box 2194, Folder 2)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 3)
  - Ivy Day, 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 4)
  - Class Letters, 1958-2002 (Box 2194, Folder 5)
  - Mailing Lists (Box 2195.2)
    Restricted to protect donor privacy.
  - Nominating Committee, 1964-1979 (Box 2194, Folder 12)
  - Class Officers, 1954-1994 (Box 2194, Folder 6)
  - Class Officers-Photographs, 1950-1954 (Box 2194, Folder 7)
  - Organization, 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 8)
    See also Class of 1949 Organization
  - Class President, 1962-1984 (Box 2194, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaires, 1964; 1969; 1974 (Box 2194, Folder 10)
  - Questionnaires, 1970-1977 (Box 2194, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 2195, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 2195, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 2195, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 2195, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1974-1984 (Box 2195, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 2194, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 2195, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1984 (Box 2194, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2194, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2195, Folder 7)
  - 50th Reunion Book (Box 2195.3)
  - Class Secretary's Notebooks (Box 2195.1)
  - Songs, 1964; undated (Box 2194, Folder 16)
  - Special Gifts Committee, 1977-1988 (Box 2194, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer, 1959-1980 (Box 2194, Folder 18)
  - Who's Who, 1950 (Box 2194, Folder 19)
  - Year Book, 1954 (Box 2194, Folder 20)
  - Individuals A-Ed (Box 2196)
  - Individuals Ep-Ka (Box 2196.1)
  - Individuals Ke-Z (Box 2197)
  - Smith, Carol Virginia (Box 2198)
- Class of 1955 Records, 1951-2005; 1.25 linear feet (5 containers)
  The Class of 1955 was the seventy-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1955 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1955, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Clipping, 1977 (Box 2199, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Music, 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 4)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1955 (Box 2199, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1951-1952 (Box 2199.1, Folder 6)
  - Groups, 1951-1955; 1978 (Box 2199.1, Folder 7)
  - History, 1977 (Box 2199.1, Folder 8)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 9)
  - Illumination Night, 1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 12)
  - Junior Ushers, 1954 (Box 2199.1, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters, 1966-2004 (Box 2199.1, Folder 14)
  - Officers, 1952-1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 15)
  - Organization, 1951-1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 2199.1, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 2199.1, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 2199.1, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 2199.1, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 2199.1, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1980 (Box 2199.1, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1995-2000 (Box 2199.1, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 2005 (Box 2199.1, Folder 24)
  - Senior Prom, 1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 25)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1953 (Box 2199.1, Folder 26)
  - Class Supper, 1955 (Box 2199.1, Folder 27)
  - Who's Who, 1951 (Box 2199.1, Folder 28)
  - Individuals A-Z (Box 2200)
  - Anderson, Jane (thesis, "A Study of Alberti 's and Leonardo's Ideas on Painting and Their Relationship to the Early Works of Titian") (Box 2201.1)
  - Bernhardt, Joyce (post grad) (Box 2201)
- Class of 1956 Records, 1952-2002; 2.083 linear feet (7 containers)
  The Class of 1956 was the seventy-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1956 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1956, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Clippings, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Play, "Uncle Vanya", 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Speaker, Archibald MacLeish, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Dance, 1952 (Box 2202, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1952-1953 (Box 2202, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Rules Test, 1952-1953 (Box 2202, Folder 6a)
  - Groups, 1952-1956 (Box 2202, Folder 7)
  - History, 1977 (Box 2202, Folder 8)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1955 (Box 2202, Folder 11)
  - Class Letters, 1967-1976 (Box 2202, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters, 1998-2002 (Box 2202, Folder 14)
  - Officers-Photographs, 1952; 1981 (Box 2202, Folder 15)
  - Organization, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 16)
  - Poem, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 2202, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 2202, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1976 (Box 2202, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1981 (Box 2202, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1986 (Box 2202, Folder 21a)
  - Reunions, 1991 (Box 2202, Folder 21b)
  - Reunions, 1996 (Box 2202, Folder 21c)
  - Rules and Regulations [annotated], 1954-1955 (Box 2202, Folder 21d)
  - Class Secretary's Records, A-Z (Box 2202.1)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Non-Grads A-Z (Box 2202.2)
  - Songs, 1953 (Box 2202, Folder 22)
  - Supper, 1956 (Box 2202, Folder 23)
  - Who's Who, 1952 (Box 2202, Folder 24)
  - Individuals A-N (Box 2203)
  - Individuals O-Z (Box 2203.1)
  - Azevedo, Eleanor Diane (memorabilia book) (Box 2204)
  - Rawlings, Sarah (photograph album) (Box 2204)
  - Young, Leanna (scrapbook) (Box 2204.1)
- Class of 1957 Records, 1953-2002; 13.625 linear feet (17 containers)
  The Class of 1957 was the seventy-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1957 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1957, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, surveys, and other memorabilia.
  - Alumnae Fund-Special Gifts Committee, 1972-1984 (Box 2205, Folder 1)
  - Alumnae Officers, undated (Box 2205, Folder 2)
  - Calendar of Events, 1956-1957 (Box 2205, Folder 3)
  - Class Cards and Alumnae Lists, 1981 (Box 2205, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 5)
  - Commencement-Music, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 6)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 7)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 8)
  - Dinner, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1953-1954 (Box 2205, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1953 (Box 2205, Folder 11)
  - Gold Key Guides-Photographs, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 12)
  - Groups, 1953-1957 (Box 2205, Folder 13)
  - History, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 14)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 15)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 16)
  - Junior Ushers, 1956 (Box 2205, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1966-1984; 2002 (Box 2205, Folder 18)
  - Class Letters-Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 2205, Folder 19)
  - Officers, 1953-1954 (Box 2205, Folder 20)
  - Organization, undated (Box 2205, Folder 21)
  - Picnics and Luncheons, 1967; 1978 (Box 2205, Folder 22)
  - Posture Picture Study, 1981 (Box 2205, Folder 23)
  - Class President's Records, 1972-1982 (Box 2205, Folder 24)
  - Rally Day, 1957 (Box 2205, Folder 25)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 2205, Folder 26)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 2205, Folder 27)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 2206, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1977 (Box 2206, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Alumnae Fund, 1977 (Box 2206, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Alumnae Fund Committee, 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 5)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 6)
  - Reunions-Reunion Book, 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Survey, 1982 (Box 2206, Folder 8)
  - Reunion Scrapbook, 1980's (Box 2211.8)
  - Reunion Scrapbook-30th Reunion, 1987 (Box 2211.9)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2206, Folder 9)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1992 (Box 2206, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1997-2002 (Box 2206, Folder 11)
  - Reunion Photo Album (Box 2211.10)
  - Scrapbook (Box 2211.4)
  - Scrapbook (Box 2211.5)
  - Scrapbook (Box 2211.6)
  - Scrapbook (Box 2211.7)
  - Secretary, 1972 (Box 2206, Folder 12)
  - Songs, 1955-1957 (Box 2206, Folder 13)
  - Sophomore Push, 1955 (Box 2206, Folder 14)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1955 (Box 2206, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer's Records, 1972-1984 (Box 2206, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who, 1953 (Box 2206, Folder 17)
  - Individuals A-J (Box 2207)
  - Individuals K-Z (Box 2208)
  - Brackett, Cynthia (scrapbook) (Box 2211.1)
  - Kuhlthau, Margaretta (course notes, exams) (Box 2209)
  - Kuhlthau, Margaretta (course notes, exams) (Box 2210)
  - Smith, Laura Ashton (Southern Mountain Workship materials) (Box 2211)
  - Strah, Virgina L ("Concerto for Oboe and String Orchestra") (Box 2211.2)
  - Stroh, Virgina L ("Triad for Harpsichord") (Box 2211.3)
- Class of 1958 Records, 1954-2003; 3.292 linear feet (6 containers)
  The Class of 1958 was the eightieth graduating class of Smith College.